Guide to Records Concerning Real Property and Legal Transactions near Cripple Creek, Colorado
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Records of Unidentified Abstract Companies, 1861-1940; Series II; 32.9; (107 boxes)
  - Abstract Records of El Paso County, 1883-1899
    - Abstracts of Legal Instruments by Date, 1895-1899
      - Second Set, 1895-1899
        - Volume 9, Pages 1-499, Entries 11996-14182, 1896 March 28-April 14 (Box 96, Folder 249)
        - Volume 9, Pages 501-1000, Entries 14183-16430, 1896 April 14-May 5 (Box 96, Folder 250)
        - Volume 10, Pages 1-250, Entries 16431-17670, 1896 May 5-19 (Box 97, Folder 251)
        - Volume 10, Pages 251-500, Entries 17671-18933, 1896 May 19-June 3 (Box 97, Folder 252)
        - Volume 10, Pages 501-1000, Entries 18934-21348, 1896 June 3-July 3 (Box 97, Folder 253)
        - Volume 11, Pages 1-500, Entries 21349-23851, 1896 July 3-August 15 (Box 97, Folder 254)
        - Volume 11, Pages 501-1000, Entries 23852-26418, 1896 August 15-September 25 (Box 98, Folder 255)
        - Volume 12, Pages 1-500, Entries 26419-29100, 1896 September 25-November 16 (Box 98, Folder 256)
        - Volume 12, Pages 501-1000, Entries 29101-31721, 1896 November 16-December 24 (Box 98, Folder 257)
        - Volume 13, Pages 1-500, Entries 31722-34638, 1896 December 24-1897 February 5 (Box 99, Folder 258)
        - Volume 13, Pages 501-1000, Entries 34639-37352, 1897 February 5-March 27 (Box 99, Folder 259)
        - Volume 14, Pages 1-500, Entries 37353-40077, 1897 March 27-May 25 (Box 99, Folder 260)
        - Volume 14, Pages 501-1000, Entries 40077-42942, 1897 May 25-July 28 (Box 100, Folder 261)
        - Volume 15, Pages 1-500, Entries 42943-45650, 1897 July 28-October 1 (Box 100, Folder 262)
        - Volume 15, Pages 501-1000, Entries 45651-48416, 1897 October 1-December 7 (Box 100, Folder 263)
        - Volume 16, Pages 1-500, Entries 48417-51650, 1897 December 7-1898 February 1 (Box 101, Folder 264)
        - Volume 16, Pages 501-1000, Entries 51651-54411, 1898 February 2-March 29 (Box 101, Folder 265)
        - Volume 17, Pages 1-500, Entries 54412-57097, 1898 March 29-June 3 (Box 101, Folder 266)
        - Volume 17, Pages 501-1000, Entries 57098-59520, 1898 June 3-August 12 (Box 102, Folder 267)
        - Volume 18, Pages 1-500, Entries 59521-61808, 1898 August 12-October 19 (Box 102, Folder 268)
        - Volume 18, Pages 501-1000, Entries 61809-64405, 1898 October 19-December 28 (Box 102, Folder 269)
        - Volume 19, Pages 501-1169, Entries 67004-70996, 1899 March 1-August 16 (Box 103, Folder 270)
          Includes tipped in a decree from the District Court of El Paso County in The Mt. Roan Mining, Milling and Land Company versus John D. O'Haire, Jeremiah O'Driscoll, and J. W. Glackin.
      - Third Set, 1896-1899
        - Entries 1000-1999, 1896 January 21-27 (Box 104, Folder 271)
        - Entries 47000-47999, 1897 November 5-29 (Box 104, Folder 272)
        - Entries 48000-48999, 1897 November 29-December 20 (Box 104, Folder 273)
        - Entries 49000-50487, 1897 December 20-1898 January 11 (Box 104, Folder 274)
        - Entries 50488-52000, 1898 January 11-February 9 (Box 104, Folder 275)
        - Entries 52001-52999, 1898 February 9-28 (Box 104, Folder 276)
        - Entries 53000-53999, 1898 February 28-March 22 (Box 104, Folder 277)
        - Entries 54000-54999, 1898 March 22-April 11 (Box 105, Folder 278)
        - Entries 55000-55999, 1898 April 11-May 4 (Box 105, Folder 279)
        - Entries 56000-56999, 1898 May 4-31 (Box 105, Folder 280)
        - Entries 57000-57999, 1898 June 1-28 (Box 105, Folder 281)
        - Entries 58000-58999, 1898 June 28-July 27 (Box 105, Folder 282)
        - Entries 59000-59999, 1898 July 27-August 26 (Box 105, Folder 283)
        - Entries 60000-60999, 1898 August 26-September 26 (Box 105, Folder 284)
        - Entries 61000-61999, 1898 September 26-October 25 (Box 106, Folder 285)
        - Entries 62000-62999, 1898 October 25-November 23 (Box 106, Folder 286)
        - Entries 63000-63999, 1898 November 23-December 19 (Box 106, Folder 287)
        - Entries 64000-64999, 1898 December 19-1899 January 9 (Box 106, Folder 288)
        - Entries 65000-65999, 1899 January 9-February 3 (Box 106, Folder 289)
        - Entries 66000-66999, 1899 February 4-March 1 (Box 106, Folder 290)
        - Entries 67000-67999, 1899 March 1-27 (Box 106, Folder 291)
        - Entries 68000-68999, 1899 March 27- May 3 (Box 107, Folder 292)
    - Sale Records for Delinquent Taxes, 1896-1898
      Documents the sale of property for delinquent taxes in EL Paso County.
      - Tax Sale Record, El Paso County, 1896 December 10-1898 December 6 (Box 108 Oversize)
        First portion documents Book 5 for the sale of property for delinquent taxes on December 10-11, 1896, with certificate entries 1-1420.
        Second portion documents Book 6 for the sale of property for delinquent taxes on December 11-13, 1897, with certificate entries 1-1441.
        Third portion documents Book 7 for the sale of property for delinquent taxes on December 5-6, 1898, with certificate entries 1-1700.
  - Abstract Records of Fremont County, 1886-1899
    Records related to legal instruments applied to real estate in Fremont County. Many of these records were likely compiled by unidentified abstract companies.
    This subseries is arranged under three headings: Abstracts of Legal Instruments by Date, Sale Records for Delinquent Taxes, and Survey Notes.
    Fremont County was one of the original seventeen counties created by the Colorado legislature on November 1, 1861.
    - Abstracts of Legal Instruments by Entry Number and Type, 1886-1899
      Arranged sequentially by entry number.
      Consists of volumes with mimeograph pages of abstracts of legal instruments in Fremont County arranged by date that likely document real estate within or adjoining the Cripple Creek region.
      - Entries 1-999, 1886 May 20-1899 December 22 (Box 109, Folder 293)
        Entries 1-98 record varied legal instruments
        Entries 99-999 record discovery and location certificates for mines, including a series for placer mines in entries 4513-4598.
      - Entries 1000-2001 (Discovery and Location Certificates for Mines), 1893 November 13-1896 January 7 (Box 109, Folder 294)
        Laid-in notes relate to the Josephina Lode, May 21, 1894, on the back of a paper announcing the move of The El Paso and Fremont Abstract Co., April 25, 1896.
      - Entries 2002-2999 (Discovery and Location Certificates for Mines), 1896 January 7-March 18 (Box 109, Folder 295)
      - Entries 3000-3998 (Discovery and Location Certificates for Mines), 1896 March 18-1897 February 7 (Box 109, Folder 296)
      - Entries 3999-4999, 1896 September 18-1899 June 24 (Box 110, Folder 297)
        Entries 3999-4875 record discovery and location certificates for mines, including a series for placer mines in entries 4513-4598.
        Entries 4876-4999 record conveyances of mining deeds.
      - Entries 5000-5998 (Conveyances of Mining Deeds), 1892 July 11-1897 September 20 (Box 110, Folder 298)
      - Entries 5999-7000, 1892 September 13-1899 September 26 (Box 110, Folder 299)
        Entries 5999-6313 record conveyances of mining deeds.
        Entries 6314-6462 record quit claim deeds.
        Entries 6463-6604 record bell notices.
        Entries 6605-6806 record sweet notices (notices of action).
        Entries 6809-7001 record labor affidavits.
      - Entries 7001-7998, 1895 December 28-1899 March 3 (Box 110, Folder 300)
        Entries 7001-7510 record labor affidavits.
        Entries 7511-7998 record incorporation actions.
      - Entries 7999-8774, 1892 January 2-1899 August 4 (Box 110, Folder 301)
        Entries 7999-8065 record incorporation actions.
        Entries 8066-8774 record varied legal instruments.
    - Sale Records for Delinquent Taxes, 1893-1900
      - Tax Sale Record, Fremont County, Entries 1881-3503 and 1-1420, 1893 December 3-1900 December 8 (Box 111 Oversize)
        Second portion documents the sale of property for delinquent taxes in Fremont County from December 3, 1893, to December 13, 1898, certificate entries 1881-3503, for properties that later became part of Teller County after its founding on March 23, 1899.
      - Tax Sale Record, Fremont County, Entries 1421-4142, 1900 December 6-7 (Box 112 Oversize)
    - Survey Notes, 1895-1896
      - Approved Notes Book I, 1895-1896 (Box 113)
        Volume of carbon copies of survey notes for lodes in Fremont County.
        Includes an index to the surveys that includes an alphabetical list of lode names, as well as the claimants and survey numbers.
        Many of the notes are faded and unreadable.
  - Abstract Records of Teller County, 1891-1937
    Records related to legal instruments applied to real estate in Teller County. Many of these records were likely compiled by unidentified abstract companies.
    This subseries is arranged under seven headings: Day Book and Indices; Abstracts of Legal Instruments Related to Mines and Locations; Abstracts of Legal Instruments by Type; Abstracts of Legal Instruments by Date and Type; Sets of Abstracts of Legal Instruments by Date; Delinquent Tax Lists; and Sale Records for Delinquent Tax.
    Created in 1899, Teller County consists of the western slope of Pikes Peak.
    - Day Book and Indices, circa 1892-1899
      - Day Book, 1892 December 27-1896 March 3 (Box 114)
        Ledger with entries for debits and credits probably created by the Teller County Clerk, apart from pages 1-8, which document the daily finances of the Wilson Machinery Company, Cripple Creek, Colorado, June 17 to August 18, 1892.
        Pages 9-29 document daily finances, December 27, 1892-October 2,1893.
        Pages 35-73 are the names of mines grouped roughly alphabetically, with additional entries on pages 80, 84, 94, 102
        Pages 86-93 document daily finances, February 5-March 3, 1896.
        Pages 103-134 document a list of land not partitioned?
        Page 300-101 document daily finances, January 30-February 5.
      - Index to Mining Claims, circa 1892-1899 (Box 115 Oversize)
        Index to legal instruments for mines in Teller County and filed in Fremont County before the formation of Teller County on March 23, 1899.
      - Judgment Index, 1897-1900 (Box 116, Folder 302)
        Ledger of judgments, probably in Teller County, as well as locations formerly in El Paso County, which documents the defendant, plaintiff, case number, legal remedies, usually compensatory damages, and the date satisfied.
        Entries grouped alphabetically by the surname or corporate name of the defendant.
      - Journal of Various Lode Names and a Cash Journal, circa 1898-1927 March (Box 116, Folder 303)
        Missing pages 1-68.
        Pages 69-134 documents lodes, probably in Teller County, each with a list of legal instructs applied to the lode, circa 1898-1927.
        Pages 100-103, which document a cash journal, November 15, 1909, to December 17, 1910.
      - Index to Corporations, 1899 April-1922 July (Box 117, Folder 304)
        Index to legal instruments related to incorporation, probably in Teller County, including articles of incorporation, amendments, and dissolutions.
        Entries grouped alphabetically by the corporate name.
      - Index to Powers of Attorney, circa 1899 (Box 117, Folder 305)
        Index to legal instruments related to grants of power of attorney, probably in Teller County.
        Each entry has been struck out in pencil.
        Entries grouped alphabetically by the principal granting the power.
      - Mining Claim Owners and Assessments, M-Z, 1907-1911 (Box 118 Oversize)
        Ledger of mining claims, probably in Teller County, which includes: the name of the claim; survey number; acreage; and the section, township, and range of the claim; as well as its own and value per acre for each year, 1907-1911.
      - Index to Miscellaneous Towns and Additions, undated (Box 119 Oversize)
        Index to property lots in towns, additions, and subdivisions. Settlements include Anaconda, Cripple Creek, Florissant, Highland Grove, Independence, Lanter City, Victor, and Woodland Park.
      - Index to Mining Claims, No. 3, undated (Box 120 Oversize)
        Alphabetical index of mines that record entry numbers of conveyences.
    - Abstracts of Legal Instruments Related to Mines and Locations, 1891-1906
      Abstracts of legal instruments arranged roughly alphabetically by mine names and bound in volumes.
      Each volume includes a list of lodes and locations with abstracts in the volume.
      - Ranges 68-69-70-71, Pages 1-1247, circa 1891-1906 (Box 121, Folder 306)
      - C-D-E, Pages 2002-3170, circa 1891-1906 (Box 121, Folder 307)
      - F-G-H, Pages 3171-4177, circa 1891-1906 (Box 122, Folder 308)
      - H-I-J-K, Pages 4178-5093, circa 1891-1906 (Box 122, Folder 309)
      - S-T-U-V, Pages 9086-10096, circa 1891-1906 (Box 123, Folder 310)
      - V-W-X-Y-Z, Pages 10097-10620, circa 1891-1906 (Box 123, Folder 311)
    - Abstracts of Legal Instruments by Type, 1893-1896
      - Book 155, Book 156, and Book 157, 1893 January 3-1896 June 14 (Box 124, Folder 312)
        Bound volume with abstracts from three books.
        Book 155 abstracts deeds of trust March 6, to July 14, 1896.
        Book 156 abstracts mining deeds January 3, to June 2, 1893
        Book 157 abstracts trustee deeds, June 28, 1893, to January 11, 1896.
    - Abstracts of Legal Instruments by Date and Type, 1884-1899
      Abstracts for legal instruments for mines Teller County and filed in El Paso and Fremont Counties for legal acts before the formation of Teller County on March 23, 1899. Some entries were filed in Fremont County after the formation of Teller County.
      Each entry has two numbers: a sequential number and another number that references a filing number.
      Arranged sequentially by title on the spine of the volume.
      - Volume F0, Entries 1-997 (14301-52293), 1884 July 10-1899 December 12 (Box 125, Folder 313)
        Entries 1-98 (14301-52293) are not sequentially or chronologically arranged in the volume and abstract mine locations, July 10, 1884, to December 12, 1899.
        Entries 99-997 (22636-26360) abstract mine locations November 12, 1891, to November 9, 1893.
      - Volume F1, Entries 998-2001 (26365-33404), 1893 November 10-1896 January 7 (Box 125, Folder 314)
      - Volume F2, Entries 2002-2999 (33408-36278), 1896 January 7-March 18 (Box 125, Folder 315)
      - Volume F3, Entries 3000-3998 (36279-42387), 1896 March 18-1897 February 27 (Box 125, Folder 316)
      - Volume F4, Entries 3999-4999 (23326-53561), 1896 September 18-1900 April 23 (Box 125, Folder 317)
        Entries 3999-4512 (40462-53561) abstract mine locations November 12, 1891, to April 23, 1900
        Entries 4513-4598 (23328-47772) abstract placer mine locations April 6, 1892, to March 11, 1899.
        Entries 4599-4725 (34466-48555) abstract mine locations with amendments February 1, 1896, to November 29, 1898.
        Entries 4726-4875 (34373-49960) abstract mine locations with amendments and additions January 31, 1896, to March 23, 1899.
        Entries 4876-4999 (23326-27655) abstract conveyances of mine deeds April 6, 1892, to April 30, 1894.
      - Volume F5, Entries 5000-5998 (27656-44438), 1894 April 30-1897 September 20 (Box 126, Folder 318)
        Abstract conveyances of mine deeds.
      - Volume F6, Entries 5999-7000 (44504-51606), 1892 September 13-1899 September 26 (Box 126, Folder 319)
        Entries 5999-6313 (44504-51606) abstract conveyances of mine deeds September 28, 1897, to September 26, 1899.
        Entries 6314-6462 (24360-49669) abstract quit claim deeds September 13, 1892, to March 6, 1899.
        Entries 6463-6604 (26457-27431) abstract bell notices December 4, 1893, to April 3, 1894.
        Entries 6605-6806 (28869-31534) abstract sweet notices September 27, 1894, to July 5, 1895.
        Entries 6807-7000 (24849-33476) abstract labor affidavits December 27, 1892, to January 9, 1896.
      - Volume F7, Entries 7001-7511 (33477-50078), 1894 February 1-1899 March 3 (Box 126, Folder 320)
        Entries 7001-7510 (33477-50078) abstract labor affidavits January 9, 1896, to March 3, 1899.
        Entries 7511-7998 (23376-43327) abstract acts of incorporation and certificates of paid stock February 1, 1894, to May 12, 1897.
      - Volume F8, Entries 7999-8831 (24858-49809), 1892 January 1-1899 March 15 (Box 126, Folder 321)
        Entries 7999-8065 (43328-49809) abstract acts of incorporation and certificates of paid stock May 12, 1897, to March 13, 1899.
        Entries 8066-8676 (30033-45785) are not chronologically arranged, although some sequences have a general chronological organization. The entries abstract various legal instruments, January 1, 1892, to March 15, 1899.
        Entries 8677-8761 (32564-38763) abstract mining location certificates November 30, 1895, to May 26, 1896.
        Entries 8762-8775 (31113-48727) abstract judgments May 9, 1895, to December 17, 1898.
        Entries 8776-8831 (24858-30215) are not chronologically arranged, although some sequences have a general chronological organization. The entries abstract mine surveys October 5, 1894, to December 2, 1898.
    - Abstracts of Legal Instruments by Date, 1899-1933
      Material under this heading is arranged into two sets: First Set, 1899-1917; and Second Set, 1899-1933.
      - First Set, 1899-1917
        - Volume 0, Entries 1-1000, 1899 April 1-May 10 (Box 127, Folder 322)
        - Volume 1, Entries 1001-2000, 1899 May 10-June 12 (Box 127, Folder 323)
        - Volume 2, Entries 2001-2999, 1899 June 12-July 15 (Box 127, Folder 324)
        - Volume 3, Entries 3000-3999, 1899 July 15-August 14 (Box 127, Folder 325)
        - Volume 4, Entries 4000-4999, 1899 August 14-September 9 (Box 127, Folder 326)
        - Volume 5, Entries 5000-5999, 1899 September 9-October 3 (Box 127, Folder 327)
        - Volume 6, Entries 6000-6999, 1899 October 3-21 (Box 127, Folder 328)
        - Volume 7, Entries 7000-7999, 1899 October 21-November 13 (Box 128, Folder 329)
        - Volume 8, Entries 8000-8999, 1899 November 13-December 4 (Box 128, Folder 330)
        - Volume 9, Entries 9000-9999, 1899 December 4-26 (Box 128, Folder 331)
        - Volume 10, Entries 10000-10999, 1899 December 26-1900 January 11 (Box 128, Folder 332)
        - Volume 11, Entries 11000-11999, 1900 January 11-31 (Box 128, Folder 333)
        - Volume 12, Entries 12000-12999, 1900 January 31-February 24 (Box 128, Folder 334)
        - Volume 13, Entries 13000-13999, 1900 February 24-March 21 (Box 128, Folder 335)
        - Volume 14, Entries 14000-14999, 1900 March 21-April 16 (Box 129, Folder 336)
        - Volume 15, Entries 15000-15999, 1900 April 16-May 10 (Box 129, Folder 337)
        - Volume 16, Entries 16000-16999, 1900 May 10-June 5 (Box 129, Folder 338)
        - Volume 17, Entries 17000-17999, 1900 June 5-July 2 (Box 129, Folder 339)
        - Volume 18, Entries 18000-18999, 1900 July 2-31 (Box 129, Folder 340)
        - Volume 19, Entries 19000-19996, 1900 July 31-August 27 (Box 129, Folder 341)
        - Volume 20, Entries 19997-20993, 1900 August 27-September 21 (Box 129, Folder 342)
        - Volume 21, Entries 20994-21998, 1900 September 21-October 18 (Box 130, Folder 343-344)
        - Volume 22, Entries 21999-22996, 1900 October 18-November 16 (Box 130, Folder 345-346)
        - Volume 23, Entries 22997-23999, 1900 November 16-December 13 (Box 130, Folder 347-348)
        - Volume 24, Entries 24000-24999, 1900 December 14-1901 January 3 (Box 130, Folder 349)
        - Volume 25, Entries 25000-25991, 1901 January 3-25 (Box 130, Folder 350)
        - Volume 26 and Volume 27, Entries 26001-28009, 1901 January 26-March 23 (Box 131, Folder 351)
        - Volume 27, Entries 27008-27999, 1901 February 23-March 23 (Box 131, Folder 352)
        - Volume 28, Entries 28000-28999, 1901 March 23-April 24 (Box 131, Folder 353)
        - Volume 29, Entries 29000-30002, 1901 April 24-May 28 (Box 131, Folder 354-355)
        - Volume 31, Entries 31000-32003, 1901 July 3-August 13 (Box 131, Folder 356)
        - Volume 32, Entries 32004-33004, 1901 August 13-September 23 (Box 131, Folder 357)
        - Volume 34, Entries 34002-34997, 1901 November 1-December 9 (Box 131, Folder 358)
        - Volume 35, Entries 34998-35999, 1901 December 9-1902 January 11 (Box 131, Folder 359)
        - Volume 36, Entries 36000-36999, 1902 January 11-February 17 (Box 131, Folder 360)
        - Entries 90009-90998, 1915 October 14-1916 January 20 (Box 132, Folder 361)
        - Entries 91002-92001, 1916 January 21-April 20 (Box 132, Folder 362)
        - Entries 92002-93006, 1916 April 21-July 21 (Box 132, Folder 363)
        - Entries 93007-94003, 1916 July 22-October 25 (Box 132, Folder 364)
        - Entries 94004-95000, 1916 October 25-1917 January 26 (Box 133, Folder 365)
        - Entries 95001-95999, 1917 January 27-April 20 (Box 133, Folder 366)
        - Entries 96000-97006, 1917 April 20-August 4 (Box 133, Folder 367)
        - Entries 97007-97996, 1917 August 6-December 3 (Box 134, Folder 368)
        - Entries 97997-99000, 1917 December 3-1918 March 30 (Box 134, Folder 369)
      - Second Set, 1899-1933
        Possibly County Clerk Ledgers for Teller County
        Each volume designation is composed of four bound volumes. Each bound volume contains 250 pages.
        Bound carbon copies of typescripts.
        Also includes references to earlier entries to reflect redemptions, usually through paying taxes
        Some entries appear out of order within a few days.
        - Volume 20, Pages 1-250, Entries 480-1998, 1899 April 24-June 12 (Box 135, Folder 370)
        - Volume 20, Pages 251-500, Entries 1999-3672, 1899 June 12-August 5 (Box 135, Folder 371)
        - Volume 20, Pages 501-1000, Entries 3673-7394, 1899 August 5-October 28 (Box 135, Folder 372)
        - Volume 21, Pages 1-500, Entries 7395-11758, 1899 October 28-1900 January 24 (Box 135, Folder 373)
        - Volume 21, Pages 501-1000, Entries 11759-16107, 1900 January 24-May 12 (Box 136, Folder 374)
        - Volume 22, Pages 1-250, Entries 16108-18027, 1900 May 12-1900 July 2 (Box 136, Folder 375)
          Carbon copies of manuscript entries that are abstracts of legal instruments in Teller County.
        - Volume 22, Pages 250-500, Entries 18028-19880, 1900 July 2-August 22 (Box 136, Folder 376)
        - Volume 22, Pages 751-1000, Entries 21900-23837, 1900 October 16-December 10 (Box 136, Folder 377)
        - Volume 23, Pages 1-250, Entries 23838-25830, 1900 December 10-1901 January 22 (Box 137, Folder 378)
        - Volume 23, Pages 251-500, Entries 25831-27703, 1901 January 23-March 13 (Box 137, Folder 379)
        - Volume 23, Pages 501-750, Entries 27704-29721, 1901 March 13-May 18 (Box 137, Folder 380)
        - Volume 23, Pages 751-1000, Entries 29722-31729, 1901 May 18-July 31 (Box 137, Folder 381)
        - Volume 24, Pages 1-250, Entries 31730-33933, 1901 July 31-October 29 (Box 137, Folder 382)
        - Volume 24, Pages 251-500, Entries 33934-35961, 1901 October 29-1902 January 10 (Box 137, Folder 383)
        - Volume 24, Pages 501-750, Entries 35962-38029, 1902 January 10-March 28 (Box 138, Folder 384)
        - Volume 24, Pages 751-1000, Entries 38030-40302, 1902 March 28-July 17 (Box 138, Folder 385)
        - Volume 25, Pages1-250, Entries 40303-42583, 1902 July 18-November 28 (Box 138, Folder 386)
        - Volume 25, Pages 251-500, Entries 42584-44778, 1902 November 29-1903 March 18 (Box 138, Folder 387)
        - Volume 25, Pages 501-750, Entries 44779-47001, 1903 March 19-September 19 (Box 138, Folder 388)
        - Volume 25, Pages 751-1000, Entries 47002-48873, 1903 September 21-1904 February 20 (Box 138, Folder 389)